Rising medical expenses and paying out
of pocket can be overwhelming and may
strain your finances, especially when
unexpected health issues arise. Are you
confident that your current health care
plan can cover all your
[Music]
needs? Ease your burden with extensive
coverage for essential healthare needs
and look forward to better days with
manual life medical secure. Experience
coverage for hospital confinement,
emergency treatments, select special
procedures, and more through a wide
network of hospitals and clinics
anywhere in the Philippines. Get high
medical coverage with annual benefit
limits of 1 million pesos, 2.5 million
pesos, and 5 million
pesos. Receive extensive health
protection and life insurance for as low
as 60 pesos a day.
Enjoy free annual checkups and 247 tele
medicine
services. In the event of death, your
family will receive cash assistance
equivalent to 10% of your annual benefit
limit. Experience cashless convenience
at our nationwide accredited providers
with reimbursement options available for
nonacredited providers. Simply present
your digital card and letter of
authorization without having to pay out
of pocket. Easily manage your healthcare
with our app-based claims experience.
Access your digital card, request LOAs,
schedule checkups, and more. Get the
protection and coverage you need with
guaranteed renewal until age
75. Better days are within reach with a
plan that meets your needs and
budget. Manualife Medical Secure. Get
better with a plan you deserve. Visit
manualife.com.p PH to learn more.